Device Monitor - Linux kiosk Build
Version: dev-20251001-102640
Built: 10/01/2025 16:06:55
Platform: Linux x64
Mode: kiosk

Usage:
  ./device_monitor_linux_kiosk

Kiosk Mode:
  - Run with kiosk environment enabled
  - Use installation scripts in linux/ directory
  - Includes systemd service for auto-boot on system startup
  - Includes display manager configuration for auto-login
  - Full kiosk lockdown with Openbox window manager
  - See deployment documentation for complete setup
  - Emergency exit: Ctrl+Alt+Shift+Q


For more information, see the documentation at:
https://github.com/Vinay125219/Single_APP
